<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ens on Yingjie</title>
    <link>/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ens on Yingjie</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>IETS Test Study Note</title>
      <link>/2022/05/21/iets-test-study-note/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/05/21/iets-test-study-note/</guid>
      <description>雅思口语万能模板 Part one Question: Do you like watching films? Tips : 替换like 第一句模板： Yeah! definitely, I do enjoy watching films. I&amp;rsquo;m a massive fan of &amp;hellip;&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;m obsessed with &amp;hellip;&amp;hellip; 第二句表达： Because I think it&amp;rsquo;s the best way for me to chill out(放松</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Listening Practice</title>
      <link>/2021/12/12/listening-prictice/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2021/12/12/listening-prictice/</guid>
      <description>Prictice One Hey guys. I am Lucy from SISU. Today I&amp;rsquo;d like to talk about American TV series. when I was in college, once it was time to grab a meal.I would joyfully rush to the cafeteria, sit in corner and start watching an episode. Watching TV series is an incredible way to learn English, You get to know how native speaker and what they talk about. In this video</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is  Short Interest?</title>
      <link>/2021/04/07/what-is-short-intrest/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2021/04/07/what-is-short-intrest/</guid>
      <description>When I am reading paper, a financial concept made me very confusion, that was “Short Interest”. After looking up some explaination, I understood it and made a note.
What is Short Interest?Short interest refers to the number of shares sold short but not yet repurchased or covered. The short interest of a company can be indicated as an absolute number or as a percentage of shares outstanding. The short interest is looked at by investors to help determine the prevailing market sentiment toward a stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>the first day of my blog</title>
      <link>/2020/06/20/the-first-day-of-my-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/06/20/the-first-day-of-my-blog/</guid>
      <description>Today, I am very happy to build my blog which will share my academic idea and experience of life. When I feel lonely and meet some trouble in writing paper,I can record my confusion to mediate intense mind. So wish me have a good life.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
